# EMILIANO -—ALFONSO

### WEB DEVELOPER

# **ABOUT ME**

Music teacher and front-end fanatic who enjoys learning new technologies, creating beautiful websites and overall making the user have a good experience. When it comes to designing, I am a perfectionist. I am a person that's easy to get along with, and am always striving to be a better dev.

## **EXPERIENCE**

**Frontend Developer at SEIS S.A.** (mar 2021 - present) - Development of web apps related to the field of electricity, using Next.js in conjunction with Typescript and Styled Components.

**Teaching Assistant at Henry** (dec. 2020 - feb. 2021, may. 2021 - present) - My role is to guide students, help them understand core concepts and reinforce the theory by providing explanations and extracurricular projects.

**E-commerce Project** (dec. 2020 - jan. 2021) - Design and development of a website dedicated to selling digital videogames. Built using React, Redux, Express, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Passport, and Flrebase.

### **EDUCATION**

Henry Bootcamp (oct. 2020 - feb. 2021) - Fullstack Developer. 700+ hours of intensive learning. The technologies learned there include HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Node, Express, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Github, and the SCRUM methodology.

"Luis Gianneo" College of Music, Mar del Plata (dec. 2010 - dec. 2020) - Music Teacher

#### SKILLS AND SOFTWARE

HTML	Less & Sass	React	Node.js	PostgreSQL	Adobe XD
CSS	Tailwind CSS	Redux	Express	Git & Github	Adobe Photoshop
JavaScript	GraphQL	Next.js	Sequelize	Testing	Vue.js

# CONTACT